Previously on the show.
上集說到
The large balloon was punctured by dangerous goods,
危險品劃破了大氣球
leaving Balloon City seriously tilted.
導致氣球城嚴重傾斜
Luckily, General Balloon and Sparky worked together
幸好球將軍和沸羊羊合力
to deal with the crisis.
及時解除危機
Wolffy, who's holding a grudge against the General,
而記恨球將軍的灰太狼
wishes to seek revenge.
想要報復球將軍
Will his plan work?
他的詭計會得逞嗎？
"Flying Island: The Sky Adventure: When Wolffy Sticks to Balloon"
《奇幻天空島之》
A beautiful day starts with a good breakfast.
美好的一天從早點開始
They not only took my upgraded Sirius apart,
不但把我的升級天狼號拆了
but ruined everything inside!
還把家裡的東西都給毀了
General Balloon, wait and see!
球將軍，看我怎麼對付你
You don't know what I can do!
知道我的厲害了吧？
Wolffy, I've been so strict with you these days,
灰太狼，我這幾天這麼嚴格對待你
I thought you might hold a grudge against me.
還以為你會記恨我
Why would I hold a grudge against you, General?
將軍，我怎麼會記恨你呢？
What are you doing?
你在幹麼？
Let me help you.
我來幫你吧
Hmm? This is...
這是…
It's sunscreen.
這是…防曬油
-Let's continue. -Sure.
-我們繼續吧 -好
This time you won't get away with it!
這次你逃不掉了
What's happening?
怎麼回事？
Thank goodness.
還好沒事
Wolffy, why are you stuck to my back?
灰太狼，你怎麼會貼在我後面呢？
Why is there glue on me?
怎麼會有膠水？
Did I forget to put the dangerous goods away and accidentally got glue on me?
難道，是我沒放好那些危險品 不小心被膠水粘到了？
I'm sorry to get you into this.
不好意思，連累你了
Who cares about that?
沒什麼連累不連累的
What's important is to separate the two of us.
現在分開要緊
Stop, I'm gonna pop!
停，我會爆的
So? Why should that bother me?
你爆就爆，關我什麼事
Weslie, please help us!
喜羊羊，求求你幫幫我們吧
I'll catch you all when I'm free.
等我自由之後，馬上就把你們抓起來
Wolffy will catch us right away after we separate them.
他們分開後，灰太狼會馬上抓我們的
Why would he catch you?
他為什麼要抓你們呀？
He saved me selflessly today.
灰太狼他今天捨命救我
I don't think he'll do anything to hurt you.
我認為他不會做出傷害你們的事的
Then we'll pull from each side to separate you.
那我們一人一邊用力拉 把你們拉開吧
You'll pull me apart if you do that!
你們這樣會把我拉爆的
Yes, the General is so soft, he can't be pulled.
是啊，球將軍軟軟的，不耐拉呀
Then we just need to harden him.
把球將軍變硬不就可以了嗎？
Paddi's right, Sparky!
懶羊羊說得對呀
Are you all ready?
沸羊羊，你們準備好了嗎？
What happened?
發生什麼事了？
Sparky, why did you stop suddenly?
沸羊羊，怎麼突然停了？
It must've run out of power when transporting the dangerous goods.
應該是幫忙運輸危險品的時候 耗盡了能源
It's okay, we can refill energy.
沒關係，能源可以重新補充的
When will you finish refilling?
那什麼時候能補充好？
I'm not sure.
不知道
Don't worry, Wolffy.
不用擔心，灰太狼
It's a couple of days at most.
最多也就是幾天的事
A couple of days?
幾天？
Wake up, let me down.
別睡了，放我下去
Dad, how do you draw a dinosaur?
爸爸，恐龍怎麼畫？
Let Dad teach you.
爸爸教你
I know how to draw!
我會畫
These pens are too dangerous!
這筆太危險了
How can you draw without a pen?
沒了筆畫什麼？
Who says you can't draw without a pen?
誰說不行的？
It's safe now. You guys continue.
安全了，你們繼續
Could you leave us to have a peaceful, romantic dinner?
你可不可以讓我們安心地 享用一頓浪漫的晚餐啊？
You want romance?
你們想要浪漫？
I can help.
我能幫忙
Music!
音樂！
I've had enough. I must separate from General today no matter what.
我受夠了 今天無論如何都要和球將軍分開
What a hazardous lemon slice!
好危險的檸檬片
If I didn't dodge that, I would've melted.
躲不開的話，我就會被溶掉了
I know how to separate from him.
找到分開的辦法了
Oh, no, my lemon slice!
哎呀，我的檸檬片
Oh no, again?
不會吧？
You took the lemon slice attack for me?
你居然為了我擋住了檸檬片
You're such a good friend.
真夠朋友
Isn't this your favorite cartoon?
這不是你最喜歡的動畫片嗎？
Look!
快看看
Wolffy, you finally reacted to something!
灰太狼，你總算有反應了
What's wrong with you?
你怎麼了？
I've been stuck to the glue for too long. My skin is allergic to the glue.
膠水粘太久了，搞到我皮膚過敏了
It's so itchy.
我的背好癢啊
It's all my fault. I'll look for something to ease the itchiness.
都怪我不好，我現在去找止癢的東西
Do you want to know how to get rid of gum stuck to your shoes?
大家想知道怎麼樣除掉 鞋子上的口香糖嗎？
Let me tell you.
那就讓我來告訴你吧
You just need a hot water bath.
只需用一盤熱水
I know how to separate us!
我知道怎樣分開了
Are you ready? Hurry up!
你準備好了沒有啊？快點了
This...
這個…
This is too dangerous, but...
太危險了，可是…
Wolffy saved me from the lemon slice.
剛剛灰太狼 捨身幫我擋住了檸檬片救了我
My back's so itchy!
我的背好癢啊
Okay, I'll take this risk for you, my friend.
好吧，為了你這個朋友 我願意冒一次險
Great, I'm fine.
還好，沒事
Why isn't it working? Is the water not hot enough?
怎麼不管用啊？難道是水不夠熱？
Don't make it any hotter!
不要再加熱了！
How can we separate if we don't heat up the water?
不加熱一點怎麼分開啊？
It's so hot!
好燙啊！
Great, we've finally separated!
太好了，總算分開了
I think you grew bigger.
你好像變大了
I said no more heat! I expand when it's hot.
都說不要再加熱了 我遇熱就會膨脹變大
Don't push me!
不要擠我啊
Not like I want to!
我也不想啊
Don't get any larger! Sirius will explode if this goes on!
別再脹大了 這樣下去的話天狼號會爆的
I can't control myself either!
我也控制不了我自己了呀
Great!
太好了！
You have an idea?
想到辦法了？
Of course!
當然了！
I'll have to sacrifice you.
只能犧牲你了！
I can't breathe!
呼吸不了了
Thank you Wolffy!
謝謝你灰太狼
Not only did you save my life, you've also unleashed my potential!
你不但救了我的命 還讓我激發了我的潛能
I didn't know I could get this big.
我都不知道原來我可以脹得這麼大
Thank you, Wolffy!
謝謝你，灰太狼
Breakfast by myself.
獨自一個人的早餐
A brand-new fork on the table.
嶄新的叉子放桌上
Why are you still here?
你怎麼還在這啊？
This fork is too sharp, you'll get hurt easily.
這叉子太尖了，很容易受傷的
But since you saved me, I'll protect you from now on.
不過既然你救了我，那接下來的日子 我會好好保護你的
No!
不！
TO BE CONTINUED 2756 DAYS FROM SETTING SAIL
（未完待續 距離啟航還剩2756天）